

CONTACT ME AT

- Portharcourt Rivers state
 Nigeria
- Princewhyte02@gmail.com
- 09059835654
- in @princewhyte2

SKILLS SUMMARY

- •••• Front-End web development
- •••• ASP.NET Core, NODE.JS and AZURF
- • • Android App DEvelopment
- •••• Python and Flask framework
- ••• Sql and Javascript
- •••• React, Bootstrap and Material design

AWARDS/ACHIEVEMENTS

- Sponsored by Google and
 Andela to sit for Associate
 Developer Certification (2020)
- Most Outstanding web
 developer (student) at
 CadTech computers (2017)
- Most Oustanding web developer (student) at Teencoders (2019)

PRINCEWHYTE DABOTUBO

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

github.com/princewhyte2

PERSONAL PROFILE

Goal-oriented Web and Mobile Developer with strong commitment to collaboration and problem-solving.

Committed to high standards of web and Mobile design, user experience, usability and speed for multiple types of endusers. Successful at maintaining customer satisfaction through effective customer support.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CAD CONSULTING | Jan 2020 - present

- Meets with the clients to discuss the project requirements
- Sets project workflow, schedule, deliverables and -Oversees a team of five web developers

Freelance Web Developer

koothill, Teencoders and Kitobams | Jan 2014 - Sept 2017

- Managed complex projects from start to finish
- Collaborated with other designers and developers
- Translated requirements into polished, high-level websites
- Built Fintech Startup https://smartcoophq.org/ website

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Google Africa Developer Schorlarship

| March 2020 - Dec 2020

- Studied Mobile Web Specialist and Associate Android Developer Path
- Worked on creating mobile and web apps
- Fullstack Javascript web development Hong-Kong University Coursera

Ingressive For Good

| April 2020- Dec 2020

- Completed Web development Specialization
- Completed Python Specialization
- Built websites and had a deep understanding of various frameworks.